const engPitanjaLvl1 = [
    {
        question: "Plants are a source of food for humans and animals.",
        answers: {
            a: "true",
            b: "false"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which part of the plant does a seed form from?",
        answers: {
            a: "the leaf",
            b: "the root",
            c: "the stem",
            d: "the flower"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which part of the plant plays a role in its nutrition?",
        answers: {
            a: "the seed",
            b: "the root",
            c: "the flower"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "A stem is usually ________ ground.",
        answers: {
            a: "above",
            b: "under"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "What are woody plants which have leaves that do not change their green color nor lose their leaves during the winter called?",
        answers: {
            a: "deciduous trees",
            b: "evergreen trees"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What are woody plants which shed their leaves completely during the winter and regrow them in the spring called?",
        answers: {
            a: "deciduous trees",
            b: "evergreen trees"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "What are the female reproductive organs of plants called?",
        answers: {
            a: "pistil",
            b: "stamen"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "What are the male reproductive organs of plants called?",
        answers: {
            a: "pistil",
            b: "stamen"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Flowers which bear either only stamen or pistil are ________, and flowers which bear both stamen and pistil are _______.",
        answers: {
            a: "unisexual and bisexual flowers",
            b: "bisexual and unisexual flowers"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "The root of which plant is used to heal bone and tissue fractures?",
        answers: {
            a: "lungwort",
            b: "mallow",
            c: "comfrey"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Due to its exceptional healing properties, which plant is addressed by the common folk in terms: a thunder will not strike into stinging ______?",
        answers: {
            a: "chamomile",
            b: "nettle",
            c: "artemisia"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Odd One Out (a plant not used for respiratory diseases):",
        answers: {
            a: "primrose",
            b: "plantago",
            c: "marigold",
            d: "ivy"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "The leaf of which plant is used to heal wounds on the body?",
        answers: {
            a: "sage",
            b: "yarrow",
            c: "lemon balm"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What plant is popularly said to have its flowers gather the sunâ€™s rays in the middle of the summer, to give them to people during the gloomy months?",
        answers: {
            a: "the European goldenrod",
            b: "St. John's wort",
            c: "dyer's greenweed"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    }
];

export default engPitanjaLvl1